snazio.com 2003-06-04

# Privacy Statement

**_Snazzishop.com’s Privacy Policy_**  
At Snazzishop.com, your privacy is our priority. When you enter our website, you can be sure your privacy is well protected. Snazzishop.com firmly believes in protecting the privacy of our users. 

Snazzishop.com does capture or store the email contents of our users if authorised to do so by the user. The email addresses logged by the system is for system management and statistical purposes. All access to data collected by Snazzishop.com is limited. No user or third party will have access to it unless authorised in writing by the particular user or if required by law or the relevant authorities. All our employees do not have access rights to the data collected. It is our company policy that employees of Snazzishop.com do not disclose or share with third parties confidential information. Snazzishop.com does however release restricted information to the relevant bank / credit card companies / clearing houses for transaction carried by the user through the site.

To ensure total security, Snazzishop.com reviews our web security daily.

**Use of Information Gathered/Tracked**  
All information submitted to Snazzishop.com will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used to support our users' customer relationship with Snazzishop.com..

Snazzishop.com only records the email addresses for system management and statistical purposes. Information gathered on our users will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation. 

******Sharing of Information**  
Snazzishop.com does not share information about our users with any third party. However, Snazzishop.com does not control the practices of our advertisers. Should you have questions about how our advertisers use information about you when you click their ads, please contact them directly.

******Use of Cookies**  
Snazzishop.com uses cookies. The purpose of the cookies is to keep track of user ID for fast access and personalization.

******Correct/Update Policy**  
Currently, Snazzishop.com does not have a correct/update policy. 

******Delete/Deactivate Policy**  
Currently, Snazzishop.com does not offer users a means by which to completely delete personal information submitted.

******Privacy Policy Changes**  
Should there be any change to Snazzishop.com’s privacy policy, we will post the change here so that users will always know what information we gather, how we might use the information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.
